bettingpartners.com 2014-12-02

# Privacy Policy | Betting Partners

##  Betting Partners Affiliate Program Privacy Policy

Private information received by Betting Partners or any of our clients’ Sportsbook, Casino and Poker Rooms WILL NEVER be distributed to anyone or any organization. Private information WILL NEVER be sold or distributed in any form, or for any purpose unless approved by the account holder. Therefore, information collected by our clients’ Sportsbook, Casino and Poker Rooms is the property of our clients’ Sportsbook, Casino and Poker Rooms, and is not shared with any third party, including merchants.

Betting Partners is dedicated to providing useful, relevant and valuable information to our affiliates. We offer an assortment of ongoing, daily, weekly and monthly publications. By opting to receive emails from Betting Partners, affiliates are automatically subscribed to the following publications:

Special Promotional Offers (Ongoing)  
Information and/or offers on any new Sportsbook, Racebook, Casino or Poker Room bonus, promotion, or event.

Service Announcements (As Needed)  
Important messages concerning any temporary site or system outages, plus any maintenance issues that may affect the level of service.

News Releases (Ongoing)  
Breaking news and expert analysis of popular games and industry trends.

To ensure the quality of affiliate communications, Betting Partners allows affiliates to view or modify their subscription preferences at any time simply by logging into their account and selecting "Manage Subscriptions" from the "Manage Account" screen.

Affiliates can opt-out of receiving email from Betting Partners. However, there is a minimum level of communication required for affiliates to be part of our program. Everyone with a Betting Partners account receives a "Welcome" email, containing valuable account information.

If at any time an affiliate indicates that he or she no longer wants to receive communications from Betting Partners, or if he or she wishes to change or correct any previously provided information, the affiliate can email outlining the request to [support@bettingpartners.com](mailto:support@bettingpartners.com).

Qualified Betting Partners staff has access to account numbers, account holder names, telephone numbers, addresses, and email addresses. Affiliates can change their password directly on the Betting Partners website.

If an affiliate needs to change an address, email and/or telephone number, they should submit changes directly from the Betting Partners website (under "Manage Account/Change Address"). New information is verified with card-issuing banks and updated accordingly. Affiliates must ensure that card-issuing banks have their new address and phone number PRIOR to submitting their profile updates.

Affiliates who lose their account login information may retrieve it via the "Forgot your password?" option found on the "Sign In" screen of the Betting Partners website. All changes made to account holder information, whether done online or by telephone, are logged. It is the policy of Betting Partners not to change an account holder's name unless we have an official name change notification on file (e.g. marriage certificate, notice of name change).

If an affiliate becomes aware that their personal information is inaccurate, or if an affiliate would like to update or review his or her personal information, the individual may contact us using the contact information below. As a security precaution, we may request that the individual provide identifying information such as name, address, etc. Betting Partners uses cookies to track how and when affiliates use the site. Cookies are pieces of information a website transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make web surfing easier by saving passwords and other preferences. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and you'll find most major websites use them. Cookies also help us see which areas of the site are popular. We use this information to continually improve the site.

Betting Partners clients’ also log IP addresses for system administration purposes. We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our servers. The Betting Partners’ website contains links to other sites; however, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of said websites.

Betting Partners occasionally updates this Privacy Policy. When we do, we revise the "last updated" date at the bottom of the Privacy Policy. Betting Partners will obtain your opt-in consent for any updates to this Privacy Policy that materially expand the sharing or use of your personal information in ways not disclosed in this Privacy Policy at the time of collection.

**Contact Information**

If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, feel free to contact us at [support@bettingpartners.com](mailto:support@bettingpartners.com)

Last Updated: October 2011
